Stop! Kisei Chuu!
给我站住 规制虫
The recent series of incidents of stolen underwear,
最近一连串的决胜内裤遭窃事件
it is all your tricks, right?
果然全是你们搞的鬼吧
Human beings are really entangled.
这人类真是纠缠不清
I will let you know my ability!
尝尝我们这一招吧
What's this?
这是什么
They've already gone, Taoyuan,
她们过去了 桃园
you can't escape.
你们逃不掉了
Stealing a girl's important panties,
竟然偷走女孩子重要的内裤
I'll kill you!
我饶不了你们
Look at my tricks.
一击恼杀
"Crazy Peony"
「狂乱牡丹」
Enjo, did they finish the fight?
炎城他们战斗结束了吗
Give them the final blow, Kirara!
给她最后一击 云母
The guy is on his last legs,
那家伙现在已经奄奄一息了
the rest is up to you.
剩下就交给你了
I see.
我知道了
Ok.
好
That's weird.
奇怪
You are careless, human.
你太大意了 人类
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
Episode 3 "Butterfly Effect"
第三话「蝴蝶效应」
Please don't be so depressed, Hoshino.
请不要这么沮丧 星乃同学
It's not going to be easy at first.
一开始往往都不会这么顺利的
But this is the third time,
但是这已经是第三次了
why is the previous active performance gone?
那天的活跃表现跑到哪里去了呢
So anxious!
真是急死人了
Hey, Kirara,
我说云母
do you accumulate H-energy every day?
你每天都有在确实累积H能源吗
What?
什么啊
It is to say
难道说
you and Retto do nothing after that?
你在那之后和烈人什么都没做吗
What are you saying! Is this still necessary to say?
你在说什么啊 这还用说吗
No!
不行啊!
Now that you have become a hero,
既然已经成为英雄了
you can think about lustful things every day.
就一定要天天想一些色色的事情才行啊
Well,
没办法
I will teach you a unique method that can easily accumulate H-energy with Kirara.
我就传授一招云母也能轻松累积H能源的独门方法吧
That is watch "H movie"
就是看「H片」
I'm not a boy,
又不是男生
how could I watch that kind of moives!
我怎么可能会看那种东西啊
To ask a girl to do that,
竟然要女生做那种事
even if there is no shame, there should be a limit.
不知羞耻也该有个限度吧
What did you say?
你刚才说什么?
It's very big, ok?
明明这么大?
Do you still say such things with your busty breasts?
胸部这么大还说这种话?
Wait, Momoka.
百花 你等一下
Sorry, Hoshino,
对不起 星乃同学
Momola shows no mercy to people with bigger breasts。
百花对胸部比自己大的人都很不留情
What? Maihime,
你说什么 舞姬
In Kirara's eyes,
在云母眼中看来
what we do may be some silly things.
我们做的这些可能都是一些傻事
But
但是啊
everyone keeps their faith in being a hero,
大家都是抱持着信念在当英雄的
and don't say that we are shameless.
不要随便说什么我们不知羞耻
Excuse me.
打扰了
Please don't take it to heart, Hoshino.
请别放在心上 星乃同学
What are the guys doing?
那家伙搞什么啊
With such a big breast and no interest in pornography,
胸部那么大还对色情没兴趣
it's a violent thing!
这根本就是暴殄天物吧
Taoyuan Momoka is my sister,
桃园园花 我的姊姊
When I take a full score,
当我考试考满分时
she will get full marks in all subjects.
她就会在全科目拿到满分
When I set my best record in track and field,
当我在田径上刷新自己的最佳纪录时
she was confirmed to be recommended by the university track team.
她已经确定获得大学田径队的推荐资格
More than it.
不只是这样
The boys I liked before,
我以前喜欢上的男孩子
they all like my sister.
大家全都喜欢上了姊姊
The reason why I lose my temper with Kirara,
我之所以会对云母发脾气
is that she is very similar to my sister.
可能是因为她和姊姊很像吧
It is … (Increase your breasts with your boyfriend! )
这是…(和男朋友一起华丽地加大胸围吧！)
So it is.
原来如此
and like this...
然后像这样…
Look down on people!
瞧不起人啊!
Next is the secret beauty special.
紧接着是机密美容特辑
Oh, soaking in soy milk bath has the effect of increasing chest circumference.
原来泡豆浆澡有增加胸围的效果
With female hormones,
与女性荷尔蒙
isoflavones that have similar effects to estrogen.
也就是雌激素有相似效果的异黄酮
As long as it is taken directly through the skin, it can stimulate the breast,
只要透过肌肤直接摄取 将可以刺激乳腺
and maybe significantly increase the bust.
有望能够明显提升胸围喔
That's it!
就是这个
We are out, now.
我们出门了
Today is a good day for breast enhancement!
今天是丰胸的好日子
So, Let's begin!
那么就赶快开始吧
So cold!
好冰
But...
不过…
that's feel good.
感觉好像挺有意思的
Now …
接下来…
First, you need to massage in a circle.
首先要用画圆圈的方式按摩
I'm back!
我回来了
I went to home at first!
今天是我第一个到家啊
Take a bath now.
赶快来泡个澡吧
Why does soy milk taste so strong, Taoyuan?
桃园? 话说豆浆味怎么这么重
So, it's Retto.
原来是烈人啊
I've just been in the bath for long time.
我只是泡澡泡得有点太久了而已
That's weird.
奇怪…
Are you OK?
你没事吧
Shit!
糟糕
The body can’t get strong because of soaking for too long.
因为泡太久身体使不上力了
Sorry, Retto.
不好意思 烈人
Can I trouble you to pull me up?
可以麻烦你把我拉起来吗
Shit!
真是的
Thanks.
谢谢
This feeling...
这个感觉
What I saw just now, the teaching of letting boyfriend touch chest
刚才看到的让男朋友摸胸部的教学
it must be the same feel.
一定就是这样的感觉吧
I will pull, one, two...
我要拉了喔 1 2…
No...
不行…
Now, I am confused
现在意识模糊
and it makes me feel that my head in the clouds...
满脑子都在胡思乱想…
Taoyuan…
桃园…
Retto,
我说 烈人
do you also like girls with big breasts?
你果然也比较喜欢胸部大的女生吗
You misunderstood, Retto
你误会了 烈人
I just soaked my head when I wanted to drink soy milk in the bathtub
我只是在想喝浴缸的豆浆时泡昏头
and then I blurted out accidentally.
才不小心脱口而出的
I saw it on TV shows that taking a soy milk bath and massaging the breasts have a enhancement effect,
我是有在电视节目上看到 泡豆浆澡按摩胸部有丰胸效果
but I never feel inferior because of my small breasts.
但我也绝对不是因为对自己胸部小自卑…
Ok, I know it.
原来是这么回事啊
Hey , Taoyuan.
我说桃园
Here.
是
I think it’s your freedom to take a bath,
我认为要怎么泡澡都是桃园你的自由
and I will not tell anyone about today's incident,
今天的事我也不会告诉别人的
don't worry.
你放心吧
And,
而且
I don't like drink beans in the bathroom either.
我也不讨厌在浴室里面喝豆浆喔
I'm very happy that you are so considerate, Retto.
你这样体贴我是很开心啦 烈人
But it has a big reaction now.
可是那个现在反应很大喔
What? Did something go wrong?
奇怪 是故障了吗
Anyway, I’m going to get water now, don’t move.
总之我现在去拿水过来 你先别乱动
Yes,
没错
The quality of pornography
色情度的素质
is not determined only by the size of the breasts.
不是只靠胸部大小决定的
Are you Taoyuan?
你是桃园小妹吧
I'm Anno Takeshi of the Earth Defense Force.
我是地球防卫队的庵野丈
I invited you to join us.
我是来邀请你加入的
Are you misunderstanding me as my sister?
你是把我误会成姊姊了吗
I am an ordinary, Momoka.
我是才能平庸的百花
You are looking for a talented sister, right?
你要找的是有天分的姊姊园花吧
No, I'm looking for you,
不 我就是过来找你的
Taoyuan Momoka.
桃园百花小妹
You may not realize it now,
你现在或许没有自觉
but you have a heroic talent far better than your sister,
但你拥有远比你姊姊还要优秀的英雄才能
and we need your power.
我们需要你的力量
When I was chosen as a hero, I thought
当我被选为英雄时我心想
I finally found a specialty that can beat my sister.
我终于找到能赢过姊姊的专长了
I'm back.
我回来了
Why does it smell like soy milk?
怎么有股豆浆的味道
Hoshino Kirara,
星乃云母
my body is not as good as yours,
我的身材确实没有你那么好
but I'm a hero, too.
但是我也是个英雄
In terms of pornography,
在色情度方面
I will never lose to you.
我是绝对不会输给你的
That's all.
我的话说完了
By the way,
顺带一提
I haven't given up on being in shape with you.
我现在还没有放弃和你比身材喔
Yesterday, the soy milk bathing breast enhancement method mentioned in this show
昨天本节目提到的豆浆澡丰胸法
was later proved to be a rumor made out of nothing.
事后证实完全是无中生有的谣言
The wrong program content was broadcast,
播出错误的节目内容
and I apologize to the audience.
在此向各位观众致歉
What! ?
什么!?
We are Pan Chuu?
我们是内衣虫
What color is your panties?
你的决胜内裤是什么颜色呢?
It's so weird.
奇怪
What's the matter, Yuina?
怎么了吗 夕菜
how weird it is!
奇怪奇怪
I can't find my panties!
我的内衣不见了
Really?
那不是糟了吗
What can I do?
怎么办
That was something
那是我今天为了和前辈约会
I prepared specially for dating senior.
特别费心准备的耶
Wait!
等一下
Kirara!
云母
What's the matter?
怎么了
What is that?
那是什么
Excuse me.
借过借过
Shit!
真是的
Why am I doing this now?
我现在为什么要做这种事啊
It's so weird.
奇怪
You are careless, human.
你太大意了 人类
I really don't fit to be a hero.
我果然不适合当什么英雄
Sorry, Hoshino,
抱歉 星乃
I'm late.
我来晚了
Enjo? Why...
炎城? 为什么…
Why do people dress like this
有人穿成这样
running around the school？
在学校里跑来跑去
Even if you don’t want to, you will notice.
就算不愿意也会注意到啊
I didn’t expect you
没想到你竟然
to accumulate H-energy by this method!
会靠这种方法累积H能源
Not like this.
不是这样啦
But it's so good!
不过太好了
Because according to Hoshino's personality,
因为照星乃的个性
I was worried that you would always be worried about your previous failures.
我原本很担心你会一直对之前的失败耿耿于怀
But I'm not worry now.
已经不用担心了
Leave it to me next.
接下来就交给我吧
What are they doing?
这家伙搞什么啊
He always pickes this kind of time to come out to grab the lead,
每次都挑这种时候出来抢锋头
not handsome at all!
根本就一点也不帅气
I snatched it back.
我把它抢回来了
Is it yours?
这是你的吧
No, no.
不是不是
I don't have such fancy underwear.
我才没有这么花俏的内衣
What happened to the light just now?
刚才的光是怎么回事
What are you doing, Enjo?
你在做什么 炎城同学
No...
不…
Do you have any misunderstandings about me, everyone?
各位同学是不是对我有什么误会!?
What's wrong with this situation now?
现在这个状况还能有什么误会
You misunderstood.
你们误会了
In order to catch the suspicious person,
为了把可疑人物抓起来
I just huddled with Enjo,
我刚才和炎城两人挤成一团
but the prisoner took the opportunity to escape through the window.
结果犯人趁机从窗户逃走了
But
不过
The stolen underwear has been taken back, and don't worry.
被偷的内衣已经抢回来了 放心吧
I'll pay off the favor I owe you,
这样欠你的人情就还清了
while Kirara has said it.
既然云母都这么说了
I can’t believe Hoshino will help the boys to speak.
真不敢相信星乃同学会帮男生讲话
Come om!
来
Thanks, Hoshino,
谢谢你 云母
I'll be in time for a date after school.
这样就赶得上放学后的约会了
Shit! I can't take it all the time.
是是是 一直放闪真受不了
Now, Yuina,
然后就是夕菜
honestly, I want to discuss something with you.
老实说我想和你商量一件事
But it was unexpected,
不过真是想不到
Kirara asked us to discuss things, which aims to buy underwear
那个云母找我们商量事情 竟然是想要买决胜内裤啊
It's enough.
已经够了吧
You have been laughing since school until now.
你们从学校就一直笑到现在
We're not laughing at you,
我们不是在笑你
but we're happy for you.
是在为你开心啊
Because Kirara has become interested in this aspect.
因为云母也开始对这方面感兴趣了
I already said it was not like this.
我都已经说不是这样了
Hey, here you are,
来 给你
I've chosen for you.
我帮你选好了
Thanks.
谢谢
So, is it targeted at people from other schools?
所以对象是其他学校的人吗
After all, the boys in our class
毕竟我们班上的男生
are still just kids.
都还只是群小鬼嘛
No!
不是这样啦
That's high garde student.
那就是大学生啰
Has the other party entered society?
对方不会已经出社会了吧
That's it, isn't it?
这还用说吗
Treat it like this for now.
就暂时先当成是这样吧
This one, right?
真的要选这件吗
Since it is underpants,
既然是决胜内裤
it must be more sensational.
当然要能多煽情就多煽情啊
It doesn't matter.
没关系啦
Anyway, I will only show it to people I like.
反正只会给喜欢的对象看啊
I don't want to show it to people I like,
我又不是要给喜欢的人看的
it's really weird, Yunnai.
真是这样反而很怪喔 云乃
Hey, Yuina,
对了 夕菜
you have a data after school, right?
你不是说你放学后要约会吗
No problem.
没问题的
We've made an appointment to meet around here.
我已经约好在这附近碰面了
Anyway,
话说回来
I'm really curious about what kind of person Yuina is dating.
真好奇夕菜的约会对象是什么样的人呢
Certainly,
的确
Senior.
前辈
Yuina.
夕菜
Ok, let's go!
好了好了 我们赶快出发吧
Yuina is still cute today
夕菜今天还是一样可爱呢
You too.
前辈才是呢
It's kind of like Yuina's style.
还挺像夕菜的作风的
Are you coming again, Rumba?
你又跑进来了吗 伦巴
Please,
算我拜托你
You can't tell anything next.
接下来的事你绝对不能说出去
May I sleep beside you?
总之先睡在你旁边可以吗
OK.
是
First,
我先声明
don't hold strange expectations,
你可别抱奇怪的期待喔
I do this not to help you store H-energy,
我这么做不是为了帮你储存H能源
but to store my own H-energy.
是为了储存我自己的H能源
By the way, your outfit...
话说回来你这身打扮…
Even though,
就算是这样
you can't turn around.
你也绝对不可以转过来喔
OK.
我知道
Now think about it, I used to
现在想想 我以前
slept with Hoshino like this.
也曾经像这样和星乃两人睡在一起过呢
Both Enjo...
话说回来以前也曾经和炎城…
Shit!
糟糕
Fell asleep halfway through homework!
作业写到一半就睡着了
Obviously Hoshina invited me,
明明是星乃邀我来的
but I fell asleep too.
结果自己也睡着了
She always teases me,
平常老是爱捉弄我
now I want to scribble in her face in return.
我要在她脸上涂鸦回敬她
-That's funny. -No …
-好好笑喔  -不…
What's wrong with you, Retto?
你怎么了 小烈
You haven't moved since just now.
从刚才就一直定住不动啊
What do you really want to do?
你刚才到底想要做什么呢
I just watch your sleeping face is funny,
我只是看你的睡脸很好笑
and just want to do graffiti on your face.
想在你脸上涂鸦而已啊
Do what you want.
那你想涂的话就涂啊
Come on, please.
来 请吧
I don't want to do it now.
我现在没那个兴致了
I'll go to bed first.
那我先睡了
Useless!
真没用
Did not expect
没想到
I would recall the dark history of the time in this situation.
我竟然会在现在这种状况 回想起当时的黑历史
Although nothing happened at the time,
当时虽然没发生什么事
we are not elementary school students anymore.
但我们现在也已经不是小学生了
Enjo!
炎城
Indeed, I just said that I can’t turn around
确实我刚才是只有说不能转过来
Ok, I really didn’t say can’t touch me,
确实没有说不可以碰我没错
I didn't expect Enjo would do such a thing,
但没想到炎城竟然会做这种事
although it is to store H-energy.
虽然说是为了储存H能源
I have to resist screaming...
我得忍住不能叫出声…
Otherwise, people in other rooms will hear.
不然其他房间的人会听见的
You're going too far！
这样真的太超过了
Stop!
你给我适可而止…
So full.
吃得好饱…
Why is it you again, Tenkuzi Zora?
怎么又是你啊 天空寺
Excuse me,
奇怪
What are you doing in Sora's room?
你们两个在宙的房间里做什么
Your room is opposite.
就说你的房间在对面了
By the way,
先不说这个
When did you get in?
你什么时候钻进来的
I have been sleeping in it since I came back from the bathroom.
我上厕所回来后就一直睡在里面啊
In other words, from the beginning...
也就是说打从一开始…
What were you two doing just now?
你们两个刚才在做什么
I accidentally entered the wrong room.
我也是不小心进错房间了
No kidding, you should be careful.
真是的 你也小心一点嘛
I'll leave now.
那么我先告辞了
Ok, Tenkuzi Zora,
好了 天空寺
go back to your room.
你也赶快回自己房间吧
Actually, I was mentally prepared,
亏我都已经做好心理准备了
but ended up simply like this.
结果却这样不上不下地结束了
Persisting to the bottom of the matter,
追根究柢
Why did I have other girls sleeping in the room when I was past?
为什么我过去时 已经有其他女生睡在房间里了啊
Enjo … Enjo is …
炎城…炎城是…
Idiot!
笨蛋
The H-energy was finally stored,
好不容易储存起来的H能源
and the underwear just bought are wasted.
还有才刚买的内衣都白白浪费了
I finally found the courage to buy it.
我好不容易才鼓起勇气买的啊
I didn’t expect you to beat this reinforced barrier twice.
没想到你竟然两度打穿这个强化防壁
Sure enough, you have outstanding talents.
你果然拥有出色的才能
I'm not happy anymore.
这样讲我一点也不高兴
It seems that you have found a way to store H-energy.
看来你已经找到储存H能源的方法了呢
Yeah.
是啊
That's great!
真是太好了
H-moive is wonderful, right?
H片很精采对吧
No, you misunderstood.
不是 你误会了
What?
什么什么
Anything else?
不然是怎么样
It's a secret.
这是秘密
Why? Tell me please.
为什么 告诉我嘛
We're partner, right?
我们不是同伴吗
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
Next episode :"Snow White and the Color of the Universe. "
下一回「白雪公主与宇宙的颜色」